Collin Dapper

Tracy, Ca 95376 | (510)-599-3461 | collindapper@gmail.com

Website: https://collins-personal-portfolio.netlifv.app/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/collin-dapper-a1b59a152/

GitHub: https://github.com/collindapper

SUMMARY

Adaptive and creative junior full-stack web developer with proficiency in front-end programming languages such as: HTML, CSS, and ReactJS; Back-end programming knowledge in JavaScript and Ruby, as well as, conducting user research and collaborating with developers to build dynamic websites. Professional strengths include problem-solving, communication and time management. Analytical and leadership mindset from experience in Operations Management.

SKILLS

- Management

Team Leadership

JavaScript

Front-End Development

Full-Stack Development

React.js

REST APIs

JQuery

Cascading Style Sheets

(CSS)

HyperText Markup
Language (HTML)

- Dynamic Websites

Data Analysis

- Data Analysis

EDUCATION

Altcademy

Full-Stack Web Development

University of Nevada, Reno

- Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, Finance. Minor in Economics.

San Joaquin Delta College

June 2015 - December 2018

January 2018 - August 2020

November 2021 - Current

Associates in Math and Science (AA-T) / Associates in Business Administration (AS-T)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Web Developer (Student) - Altcademy

November 2021 - Current

- Developed three user-friendly websites using React JS and JavaScript, along with several other programming languages, libraries and frameworks.
- Created a dynamic shopping cart that allows the user to generate a total price from a list of inputed items and cost per item; Used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Built a movie finder using React JS as a go-to quick search for all information on movies, television shows, etc.

Manager I, Operations - Amazon.com

April 2021 - April 2022

- Coach, manage, and develop a team of 200 Amazon associates
- Communicate policies to my team and act as the primary information source for the team -maintaining compliance, consistency, and taking corrective action when needed
- Create, manage, and support recognition programs
- Support all safety programs and OSHA compliance to ensure a safe work environment for all associates
- Ensure procedures are followed for building security and product loss prevention
- Develop tools to track and analyze cost and production trends
- Partner with the management team to establish and maintain quality control standards
- Develop performance goals and objectives to achieve customer demand and ensure accuracy and quality

CERTIFICATIONS

Altcademy

- ReactJS Development Certification June 2022
- Dynamic Website Development Certification May 2022
- JavaScript Programming April 2022
- HTML CSS Development February 2022